Susan, you've got to hit
the board to pop the balloon.
Susan, throw again.
Pick another card,
don't be upset.
Throw again.
Freezer. Susan, you did it.
- Where is he?
- Oh, he'll be here.
He probably just, uh,
got caught in traffic.
I bet he ran out on me.
Probably figured the whole thing was
hopeless, he took off for the Bahamas.
My father would not do that.
He hates the Bahamas.
- Oh, you can't smoke in here.
- I tell you what, I'm not gonna light it.
I'm just gonna sit it in my
mouth and pretend. See?
Why don't you just quit?
I give up drinking, I end
up on trial for murder.
Forget it.
Besides, everybody's
gotta have at least one vice.
Otherwise the angels get jealous
and start screwing up your life.
That's true. A nun told me that.
- Where've you been?
- I'm sorry I'm late.
What the hell happened?
- I fell asleep on the couch.
- You did what?
Are you okay?
That's Paul Dodge, the man
who really killed Allan Rafferty.
Dad, we've been through this.
- No, no, no.
I know how it happened. I
just had a dream about it.
See, he wanted to frame Terry,
so he opened the door
at the end of the east wing,
knowing it would set off the
alarm at the security guard's desk.
Then he backed into the shadows.
Security guard walked down
the east wing to check the door.
Paul Dodge waited
for him to pass,
then he hurried back up
the west wing into the pool,
drowned Allan Rafferty, threw
Terry's necklace in the pool,
and then snuck back to his suite,
which was just across the hall.
It works for me.
But Dr. Dodge's rooms are in the
west. He'd have to go right past the guard
to get to the door
in the east wing.
Ben, how'd he do that?
I don't know.
Dad,
you're obsessed with the idea
that Paul Dodge did it, and
your theory doesn't work.
You're not looking at
the facts objectively.
How come you're so pale?
You're the one that keeps
telling me to stay in out of the sun.
Come on, let's get inside.
Is this the necklace
you fished out
at the clinic that night, detective?
- Yes, it is.
Were you able to ascertain
to whom it belonged?
Yes, sir. It's engraved with the words,
uh, "To Terry with love, from Linda."
And since Terry Landis
was the only Terry
staying at the, uh,
clinic at that time,
we went up to his room, asked
him if it was his, he said it was.
Did he explain to you how it was
found in the pool with Dr. Rafferty's body?
No, he said he didn't
know how it got there.
Did he suggest he might have lost it
while swimming laps or something?
No, he told us he never used the
pool, said the chlorine dried his hair out.
You've worked homicide how long?
Eight years.
In your opinion, how do you
suggest this necklace got in the pool?
You think it might have
just fallen off his neck.
Or maybe it was
yanked off accidentally
while he was
drowning Dr. Rafferty.
Could have.
Thank you, that's all.
- Mr. Matlock.
Detective,
does this, uh,
clasp look broken to you?
No.
But if it had been yanked
off in some violent struggle,
you'd think it would be
broken, wouldn't you?
Well, like he said,
maybe it just fell off.
- Off the defendant's neck?
- Yes.
Or maybe,
maybe somebody stole
this out of Terry's room,
and dropped it in the pool in
order to frame him, right, detective?
- I guess so.
- Thank you.
I understand you were a
patient at the Paul Dodge Clinic
at the time Dr. Rafferty
was murdered.
I'm still a patient there.
Now, unlike many celebrities who've
admitted themselves to the clinic,
you seem to have made
no attempt to keep it a secret.
Why is that, Miss Page?
I believe people like me set an
example, whether we like it or not.
Whatever is cool for us is gonna be
cool for the kids who dig our music.
We do drugs, they're
gonna do drugs.
We discover that that was a
mistake and go and get help,
maybe they will too.
The defendant, Terry Landis,
did he let people know he'd
been admitted to the clinic?
- He didn't want anybody to know.
- He ever tell you why?
He was afraid that it
was bad for his image.
He plays this cop on TV.
He was afraid the network would can
him if it became common knowledge
that he was a major
boozer in real life.
I understand that on
the day of the murder
Terry Landis came bursting
into a private session
you were having with
Dr. Rafferty. Is that right?
- Yeah.
- Tell us what happened.
He was angry because
the National Informer
had just come out
with a story about him.
This the story? PAGE: Yes.
He was holding a
copy of it in his hand.
He accused Dr. Rafferty of
leaking things that he had told him
during his therapy
session to the Informer.
What did Dr. Rafferty say?
- He denied it.
What did Mr. Landis say?
- He didn't believe him.
- He threaten Dr. Rafferty?
- More or less.
In point of fact, didn't he throw a punch
at Dr. Rafferty right there in the office?
Yes, but he missed.
He's not very good
with his fists in real life.
What about the necklace?
Was he wearing it?
I don't know. Seems he
wore it most of the time.
Thank you, Miss
Page. That's all.
Mr. Matlock.
No questions, Your Honor.
The witness may step down.
It's not going very well, is it?
- Oh, it's going fine.
- Oh, I know it's not.
For one thing, juror
number 10 hates me.
- Why do you say that?
- The way he looks at me.
Only directors
look at me like that.
- Directors hate me. MATLOCK:
Maybe the security guard
always takes a break
at the same time.
Maybe Paul Dodge knew that.
Maybe that's when he
snuck into the east wing.
- Dad.
- Maybe that's when he snuck
into Terry's room
and stole his necklace.
Dad, give it a rest.
Yeah. He killed two
birds with one stone.
He waited for the
guard to leave his desk.
Then he snuck out of his office in
the west wing, snuck to the east wing,
snuck into Terry's room, stole
his necklace while he was asleep,
then did that
thing with the door,
making it look like Terry
had snuck into the east wing,
snuck into the west wing, snuck
into the pool to kill Allan Rafferty.
- This is not like you.
- Why?
You never say "snuck."
Just trying to
give it a little color.
I'm gonna call that
guard right now.
Oh, this is not good.
Did you see that?
My dad walked right past a hot dog
vendor and didn't even look at him.
Something is very wrong.
Dad.
In here.
What have you been doing?
I don't know.
- You don't know?
- No.
I called the
guard, and then I...
I guess I fell asleep.
You took another nap?
The guard said that he didn't leave his
desk that night until the alarm went off.
Dr. Dodge couldn't have slipped
into Terry's room without being seen.
Why are you rubbing
your chest like that?
Heartburn or something.
- Why are you sweating like that?
- Maybe a little bit of flu.
You don't feel well?
I'm tired, Leanne. This Dodge
thing's been keeping me up at night.
Oh, nothing doing, Dad.
- You lie right back down.
- Leanne, I'm fine.
The hell you are.
I'm calling 911.
- No.
- Dad... Damn it, Dad.
- What'd they say?
- Nothing.
- No.
You tell them you
passed out this morning?
- No.
- You didn't tell them?
I didn't pass out.
What do you call falling asleep on
the couch at 10 in the morning, Dad?
I took a nap, I didn't pass out.
- Give me my clothes.
- Why?
- I'm going home.
- No.
No, no. You are
not going anywhere
until we talk to the doctor
and find out what's wrong.
There's nothing wrong
with me. It was heartburn.
- It's gone now. Give me my clothes.
- No.
Mr. Matlock.
Dr. Schoenfeld.
Well, the good news is whatever it
was responsible for your symptoms,
it doesn't appear to have
been a myocardial infarction.
- What's that?
- A heart attack.
- Give me my clothes.
- What is the bad news, doctor?
Well, the bad news is that we don't
know what caused your symptoms.
We'd like to keep you
overnight, do some more tests.
- That would be fine.
- Overnight?
- Dad.
- Now, Mr. Matlock,
it's just one night. You want to
find out what's wrong, don't you?
It was heartburn.
- It wasn't heartburn.
- Thank you, doctor.
Dad, you just rest right here.
I want you to be very comfortable.
I'm gonna take care of everything.
It was heartburn.
What about Terry
Landis' allegation
that Dr. Rafferty was selling
confidential information to that tabloid?
Allan Rafferty was a highly
respected psychotherapist
with impeccable credentials. He
would never have done such a thing.
- But if he had...
- He didn't.
But if he had, what
would you have done?
I would have fired
him on the spot.
If you'd done that, Terry
could've turned right around
and sold everything he knew about
your famous patients to the Informer.
- What are you getting at?
- Motive.
I think you suspected Dr. Rafferty
had leaked that information.
So rather than risk being embarrassed
or ruined by him in the future,
you killed him, and then pinned
the murder on Terry Landis
to discredit him and
divert suspicion from you.
I think not.
I'm right. I know
it and so do you.
You're daft, Mrs. Mclntyre.
Twenty years ago I
could've had you committed.
Once I figure out how
you got past the guard
to trip that alarm in the
east wing, I am home free.
- Oh, no one told you.
- About what?
About the envelope I
gave the guard that night.
What envelope?
I came out of my
rooms that night,
went down the hall
to the front desk,
gave the guard an envelope
that was to be picked
up at 7 the next morning.
Then I walked back
down the hall to my rooms.
What time was that?
The guard always makes
notes of such things.
I gave him the package
at exactly 10:27.
One minute later, after he watched
me walk up the hall to the west wing,
the door down the
hall, around the corner,
at the end of the
east wing was opened.
Now, these are my rooms.
Here at the end of the west wing.
Do you really think I could've
walked past that guard,
slipped past him, in
less than a minute?
I didn't know
about the envelope.
Your father knew.
I guess he forgot to tell you.
Dad?
Dad, can you hear me?
Dad. Dad.
Dad.
I didn't tell you
about the envelope.
Dad, you have got to get
this case out of your head.
Your pulse is very rapid. I think
you'd better listen to your daughter.
Did you hear that?
I'll look in on you in an hour.
Leanne, I can't stay here.
- I'm in the middle...
- We...
We. We are in the
middle of a case.
I can take care of it.
It's only for a day or two.
I hate hospitals, Leanne.
There's sick people everywhere.
You're afraid they'll find
something, aren't you?
They're not gonna find anything.
I'm afraid too.
I wish I was good at
saying stuff like this.
You're not in this alone, okay?
Hi.
- Hello, Cliff.
- Hi. How's Ben?
They're doing some tests. We'll
know more in a couple of days.
I hope he'll be okay. Here.
Does he still think
Paul Dodge is the killer?
Yeah, that's all he talks about.
Anyway, we know someone
at that clinic is the killer.
I have the feeling the only
way we're gonna find out who
is to work from the inside.
You mean send
someone in under cover
- to pose as a patient or something.
- Yeah.
Yes.
No.
No. No.
No. Leanne, I'm a lawyer,
- I'm not a spy.
- Cliff, all you have to do
is pretend like you're
screwed up for a couple of days
- and keep your eyes and ears open.
- I'm not good at pretending.
You know, when I
do, my palms sweat
and my face goes flush,
and I got chest pains, and...
- They're gonna know I'm lying.
- They'll think you're sick.
Okay.
Of course I told him everything.
Dr. Rafferty was my shrink.
Oh. So he knew all your secrets.
Maybe he didn't know them
all. But he was getting there.
It's rumored your
past is pretty colorful.
My past is a walking,
talking museum of horrors.
Come on, lady. Life is short. What
is it that you really wanna know?
What went through your mind
when Terry burst into
Dr. Rafferty's office that day
and accused him of selling
those stories to the tabloids?
Do you remember?
No, I don't.
Sure you didn't think
there might be some truth
into what Terry was saying?
And if Dr. Rafferty sold Terry out
like that, he might just sell you out too?
Are you trying to say
that I killed Dr. Rafferty?
Your room is in the east
wing, just like Terry's was.
Allan Rafferty was
no threat to me.
Like I said on the
stand, I got no secrets.
It's one thing to announce to
the world that you're an addict,
but making public why you're an
addict's got to be a lot more painful.
I'm not afraid of the truth.
Nothing happened to me
that doesn't happen to tens of
thousands of girls out there every day.
Now, as far as I'm concerned,
making that public could only help.
Now, I gotta get to
group. Tell Terry I said hey.
Well, everything
looks fine, Mr. Lewis.
Soon as Dr. Dodge talks to you, I'll
help you get settled into your room.
Uh, Dr. Dodge? The
Dr. Dodge who runs the place?
Don't worry. He interviews
all the new patients.
It's standard
operating procedure.
Now, he'll be right with
you. You just have a seat.
He's a nice guy.
You relax.
You won't find anything
of interest in there.
Mr. Lewis.
- Where'd you come from?
- From the rooms where I live.
They're through
that door. I'm sorry.
I'm Paul Dodge.
- I can explain this.
- There's no need.
Sit down. Please.
I've seen this before.
- You have?
- Of course.
Your life revolves around pills.
Pills to put you to sleep,
pills to wake you up,
pills to make you happy,
fight pain, suppress
your appetite.
That is what you were
looking for in my desk, isn't it?
Oh, boy, you're
good. You're good.
Well, I've been doing
this for a long time.
Perhaps we ought to
postpone this interview
until after you've had a
chance to settle in for a bit.
Hopefully, by then you
may be a trifle less agitated.
Why don't I just show
you to your room?
Fine. That'd be great.
This telephone will connect
you only to the front desk.
You can't make calls to
anyone outside the clinic
unless and until you've
earned that privilege.
Any questions?
- None that I can think of.
- Good.
Your bag is in the closet.
Someone will come around at 6
and show you how we do meals here.
In the meantime,
I want you to get some rest.
I will. Uh, thanks
for your help.
That's what we're
here for, Cliff, to help.
Morning, Mr. Lewis. You all set?
All set.
Is it standard operating procedure
to lock patients in their room?
Well, apparently, you were in
such a state of agitation yesterday
that Dr. Dodge felt it best
to restrict your movements.
Hey, don't worry. It
happens a lot to new patients.
I'm sure after he
finishes your evaluation
he'll grant you more privileges.
Please.
Sit.
How you feeling this morning?
Pretty good.
Don't do that.
Don't ever do that.
Don't lie to me. I know
how you're feeling.
By now you must be going
into barbiturate withdrawal.
There's no fooling you is there?
I've watched a lot of young men
and women go through this before.
- Having trouble sleeping?
- I was up most of the night.
Feeling on edge?
- You have no idea.
- Nausea?
- Uh, a little.
- Only a little?
My head feels like it's gonna explode.
There's a throbbing behind my eyes.
Maybe we should hospitalize you.
No. No, no, no, that
won't be necessary.
We want to minimize
your discomfort.
No. I'll be all right.
- Really. It's okay. Really. Really.
- All right.
All right. We'll try it here.
I'm going to assign
Dr. Hewitt to you.
I'll ask him to give you a call.
You could work out a schedule
for individual and group sessions.
I'm sure you'll make
great progress with him.
Sorry, I'm a little nervous.
I can tell.
Oh, um, about my privileges?
For the moment,
courtyard walks only
and one telephone call a
day. We'll wait till you get better.
That's... Well, I'm a little uncomfortable
with being locked in my room.
It's for your own
good, Cliff. Trust me.
Hey, you can't go out that way.
Well, way to go. You've
just set off the alarm.
Look, it says emergency exit.
I was just trying to
find the, uh, courtyard.
The door to the courtyard's
right across the hall
from the main entrance.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Hey, well, no harm done.
The security guard's
not gonna like getting up
off his keister for nothing, but
hey, he can use the exercise.
Hey, I'm sorry about the false alarm,
I'm the one who opened the door.
What door?
The emergency
exit in the west wing.
I was looking for the
courtyard. I'm new here.
Well, forget about it.
I've never seen a security
system like this before.
It's a mess.
What are you doing?
I'm moving this picture.
Come on, Dad. Let's go back
on the couch and lie down.
I don't wanna lie down anymore.
Here we go.
Now, be nice and
comfortable. There.
- Here, read a book.
- I don't want to.
Dad, you have a hiatal hernia.
The doctor told you to
lie around all weekend.
You can't tell me that moving
one little picture's bad for me.
I'm telling you to do
what the doctor said.
Now, I will have dinner
ready in a couple of minutes.
Just wanted to move
one little picture.
Hello?
Ben. It's Cliff. You're
home. Are you okay?
Yeah. You still at the clinic?
Yes, and I'm only allowed
one phone call a day,
so whatever you do, don't
hang up till I'm through, okay?
You got something?
Oh.
That's interesting.
That's very, very interesting.
Good work.
No, no. You can't
leave the clinic yet.
Maybe in a couple of days.
Cliff, Cliff, Cliff.
Even if Dr. Dodge
does suspect you,
he wouldn't do that.
They don't do
lobotomies anymore.
Just stay, okay? And keep calm.
Good boy. Bye.
Okay?
Leanne!
What? Are you okay?
- I got it.
- Got what?
I know how Dr. Dodge did it.
Dad, let me just get
dinner on the table,
and then you can tell
me all about it, okay?
But I know how he did it.
Daggone.
Oh. Dr. Dodge, hello
again. Am I, uh, interrupting?
Not at all. I have, uh, ten whole
minutes before my next appointment.
- Please sit down.
- Thanks.
You look like you
just got out of bed.
I did. I haven't
been feeling well.
Oh.
- Anything serious?
- No.
They ran some tests. The
doctor thinks I have a hiatal hernia.
It's somewhere here
in the digestive tract.
Me, I think it's this case. I've been
so obsessed with trying to figure out
who actually killed Allan
Rafferty, it made me sick.
Or maybe it's, uh, that deep
down in your heart of hearts,
you know your client's guilty.
No, no, no.
I'm more convinced than
ever that he's innocent.
I know about the door.
- The door?
- The emergency exit door
at the end of the east wing
which triggers the alarm
when nobody's even near it.
Bad connections or something.
The security guard told me
that just before the murder
it false alarmed three
times in four days.
We're just about to put in
an entire new security system.
We're putting up with
the bugs in the old one,
rather than get them
repaired, I'm afraid.
Oh.
So you knew about the problem?
Yes. Of course.
Well, that means that when you
opened the emergency exit door
at the end of the west wing,
you knew the guard would
automatically go to the door
at the end of the east wing, which
had triggered the alarm, didn't you?
Have you reached the conclusion
that I killed Allan Rafferty?
I did that a long time ago.
I just wasn't sure how
you did it. Now I am.
As with all obsessions, Mr. Matlock,
this one is ill-advised and ill-fated.
You're wrong. I can prove it.
Zoe?
Hi, Zoe. This'll
only take a minute.
Zoe Altman, I want you
to meet Ben Matlock.
- Mr. Matlock, nice to meet you.
- Hello.
Miss Altman's a patient here.
Mr. Matlock represents the man
accused of killing Dr. Rafferty.
Now, I'd like you to tell him where
you were the evening Dr. Rafferty died.
Well, I was with you. I had missed
a session, I was making it up.
At what time?
About 9:00 until almost 11.
Do you usually see
patients so late at night?
Of course not.
Since Miss Altman missed her
session in order to attend a funeral,
I felt that seeing her promptly
was of the utmost importance.
But you told the police
you were alone all evening.
Well, frankly, the media's been
having such a field day with articles
about therapists having
affairs with their patients, that I...
Well, I thought it better not even to
suggest a compromising situation.
I see. Of course. Well, I...
Dad.
There you are.
You promised me you
would lie around all weekend.
What do I have to do,
watch you for 24 hours?
I thought I had
him. I was sure of it.
Dr. Dodge.
He's got an alibi.
He didn't do it.
I'm sorry, Dad. Now, come on.
I hope you don't plan
to go swimming in that.
No, just looking around.
Like to look at half
naked men, huh?
Kind of.
Actually, I'm just taking one
more look at the scene of the crime.
Always seems to help my father.
But I'm not my father.
What are you, a cop?
An attorney. Leanne Mclntyre,
co-counsel for Terry Landis.
- You a patient here?
- Assistant chef.
But they let me use the
pool when I'm not working.
- Sam Badetcher.
- Nice to meet you.
- You swim laps every day?
- Half a mile, every day.
Except Sunday.
Holy cow.
- Would you read that for me, please?
- Sure.
- Seventy-five degrees.
- Thank you.
The other one had
nice big numbers on it
that I could read all
the way across the pool.
Why they replaced it with that
piece of junk, I'll never know.
Anyone say why they replaced it?
No. Somebody decided
they wanted a change.
Dr. Dodge, probably.
- Dad.
- Yeah?
What are you doing?
I don't feel good.
Oh.
I bet I know what'll
make you feel better.
- What?
- Seven magic words.
I was wrong, and you were right.
- About what?
- Dr. Dodge.
He did it, Dad.
Tell me something, Dr. Dodge.
How did the National Informer
find out that Terry Landis
was a patient at your clinic?
I have no idea. Maybe you
should ask the National Informer.
They're shielded from,
uh, revealing their sources.
So how about it? Who
told the National Informer
of Mr. Landis'
treatment at your clinic?
I wouldn't know, counselor.
Well, you have access
to all his therapists' notes.
I mean, his visits
with Terry and all that?
Yes. As head of the
clinic, I consult on all cases.
Yeah. There are details in
here of his early childhood,
stepfather abuse,
early alcohol abuse.
That information could only
have come from one source,
- his therapist, don't you agree?
- I told you, sir. I don't know.
- You didn't leak the story, did you?
- Absolutely not.
It would ruin you and
your clinic if word got out
that your staff was leaking patient
information to the National Informer.
- Well...
- Then when the story did come out,
you knew only one
person could have leaked it,
outside of Terry Landis himself,
and that was his
therapist, Allan Rafferty.
So rather than let his greed
destroy your clinic, you killed him.
Objection. Seems Mr. Matlock
is confused as to exactly
- who's on trial here.
- Uh, Your Honor,
the evidence against my
client is purely circumstantial.
I must be allowed to demonstrate
that those very same circumstances
might make someone else,
maybe even this gentleman
here, appear just as guilty.
- Overruled.
- Thanks.
Uh, Carter Jacobson, night
watchman there at your clinic,
ready to testify that
he discovered the body
at, uh, 11:00 that night.
Now, where were you
between, say 10 and 11?
I was in my office, conducting
a private therapy session.
Individual therapy session with a
patient, uh, Miss Altman, right over there.
Miss Altman is ready to testify
that you left your office
around 10:30, right?
I suddenly remembered
that, uh, I promised someone
I would leave a package
for them at the front desk.
She's also ready to testify
that you were gone a good five,
maybe ten minutes.
What took you so long?
I stopped off in my apartment
to make a telephone call.
There's no record of your
making a phone call that night.
The line was busy,
I never got through.
I see. I see.
So all we have is your word
that you were in your room
trying to place a call at
the time of the murder,
the same as all we have is Terry's
word that he was in his room sleeping.
The police found his necklace
in the pool that evening, not mine.
Don't you have a pass
key to all the rooms?
Yes. But...
So you could've
slipped into Terry's room,
stolen his necklace
while he was asleep,
dropped it in the pool
after you killed Dr. Rafferty.
I did not kill Allan Rafferty.
Are you sure you didn't
give the guard the envelope,
then walk up the
hall of the west wing,
open the emergency exit there,
knowing the guard would go
to the door at the east wing,
because it had
triggered the alarm,
it had done it three
times the week before
and you knew the police
would later suspect,
because of his necklace,
that Terry had done it.
You knew that nobody would
suspect that you were actually the one
who went in that pool and
drowned that wayward employee.
Mr. Matlock, I am
not an attorney,
but it seems to me you are
coming very close to slander, sir.
Close? Yeah, I'd be knee deep
in it if it wasn't for one little thing.
I've got proof.
Mr. Sam Badetcher,
assistant chef at your clinic,
is ready to testify
that there used to
be a thermometer
that hung on the north side
of the pool at the deep end.
It was there when he swam laps
the afternoon before the murder.
But there's no sign of it here,
see, in this picture the police took
of the body some
seven hours later.
He's also ready to testify that
when he swam laps the next day,
there was a new
thermometer in its place.
What happened to
the old one, Dr. Dodge?
I don't know. It, uh,
suddenly disappeared.
Yeah.
My daughter's not only a fine
lawyer, she's a fine detective.
That thermometer disappeared
because it got broken in the struggle
while you were
drowning Allan Rafferty.
It either got
broken accidentally,
or he broke it on purpose to
use as a weapon against you.
But anyway, when it was over
and your colleague was dead,
you couldn't leave it there.
Might incriminate you.
So you scooped up that broken
thermometer, took it with you.
But Miss Altman was waiting in
your office. Time was of the essence.
You could always
get rid of it later.
But you had to do something
with it right then and there.
And so you hid it.
Under the mattress in your bed.
This bed.
The one the police and
my daughter, with a warrant,
took out of your place this
morning. What do you say, doctor?
No.
Then why did the police
lab find mercury in the fibers
at the bottom of your mattress,
and in fibers at the top
of the box spring under it?
Because you got rid of that
thermometer as quick as you could
after the police left.
But the broken stem had already
leaked mercury into your bed.
And it's still there.
You killed Allan Rafferty.
I told you.
It is great to be free.
And it's a kick to know that
our system of justice works.
And not just on TV,
but in real life too.
- What are you gonna do now?
- What next?
My agent here says the
networks are gonna make my story
into a mini-series,
starring me as myself.
Thank you.
What a jerk, the guy
didn't even say thank you.
Yeah he did. Got
his check right here.
- Let's get something to eat.
- Hungry?
- I'm starving.
- Me too.
Three hot dogs, all the way.
He lives.
www.tvsubtitles.net